郑重声明：本作品之片源、字幕均来自互联网，版权归原电影公司所有。本站和制作者不承担任何法律及连带责任！任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途，否则一切后果由该组织或个人承担！请自觉于下载后２４小时内删除。如果喜欢本片，请购买正版!
乔什哈奈特吧倾情出品
字幕君:@MC_卷
[孩子的黑色气球让她飞舞]
[Music]Baby's black balloon makes her fly [music]
把衬衫折好
- Need to tuck that shirt in.
是,老师
Yes,sir.
[并且你从未考虑过明天]
[Music]And you weren't thinking about tomorrow [music]
[因为你跟我一样]
[Music] 'Cause you were the same as me [music]
←他不是   乔什哈奈特
爱在地球尽头
[无数的男孩们都无法得到你]
[Music]A thousand other boys could never reach you [music]
[我如何能成为你的唯一]
[Music]How could I have been the one [music]
[世界在你下方围绕着你旋转]
[Music]I saw the world spin beneath you [music]
[如同调羹里散开的碎冰]
[Music]And scatter like ice from the spoon [music]
[这里曾经是你的家]
[Music] There was your home [music]
[落在一个变化万千的世界]
[Music] Comin'down the world turned over [music]
[没有你危险便降临]
[Music]A dangerous fall without you there [music]
[当你害怕时我会继续]
[Music]I go on as you get colder [music]
[不论你是否在那里]
[Music] Or are you someone who's there [music]
[你知道那些他们总是对你说的谎言]
[Music] You know the lies they always told you [music]
[只有爱你从未幻想得到]
[Music] The only love you never dreamed [music]
[是他们从未给你的]
[Music] Was of things they never showed you [music]
[那些谎言吞噬着太阳的光亮]
[Music] That swallowed the light from the sun [music]
[在你世界中的光亮]  噢 有人迷路了
- [Music]Inside your world [music] - Oh,somebody's lost.
[耶]
[Music] Yeah [music]
[我落在这个翻转的世界]
[Music]I'm comin'down to a world turned over [music]
[危险降临在没有你的世界]
[Music]A dangerous fall without you there [music]
[我会继续 我会带着你朝着回家的方向]
[Music]As I go on I will lead you homeward [music]
[都是因为]
[Music]All because all [music]
[我将成为的人]
[Music]I'll become [music]
[你属于我]
[Music] You became to me [music]
车子不错  谁搞来的车子
Sweet ride. Who scored this?
也许是些他妈的被宠坏的混蛋
- Probably some spoiled-ass mother... - Shiverson!
-看看这车子镀的络合金-太赞了
-  Look at that chrome on that thing,man. - Very nice.
这个,呃......的确是个很赞的礼物
It's,uh,a very nice gift.
我想你很失望吧
I'm sure you're disappointed.
因为我爸不能来参加毕业典礼么
Why,'cause my father can't come to graduation?
他在伦敦
He's in London
正让我们公司的股票价格翻倍呢
in the middle of a deal that's gonna double our stock price.
我也不需要他来破坏某些
I don't need him to jeopardize that for some .
胡扯的毕业典礼
bullshit graduation ceremony.
不好意思 先生
Sorry,sir.
毕业典礼可不是胡扯
The graduation ceremony is not bull.
特别是当你在做告别演说时
Certainly not when you're valedictorian.
恕我冒昧 校长 我可没在这呆上4年
With all due respect,sir,I didn't spend four years here...
没必要对着一帮哀嚎的小破孩
just so I could give a "go get 'em" speech
发表励志演说
to a bunch of whining children.
好吧 那你也知道大学里对车子的规定
Well,you know the rule about cars on campus.
我得暂时把车子存到星期天的仪式过后
So I'll keep it in the motor pool until after Sunday's ceremony,
然后再还给你
and then it's all yours.
如果就这些的话
So,uh,if that's it...
我姐姐她男朋友也有这辆车 速度超快 老兄
My sister's boyfriend's got one. It's lickety,bro.
跟G-4一样拉风
It's like a G-4 in a tail wind.
我可以跟这种车上床
I can have sex with a car like that.
别把你的木头钻子在排气管里给点着
Just don't burn your wood drill on the tailpipe.
我的意思是有这辆车我可以跟个女人上床
No,I mean I could have sex with a woman if I had a car like that.
Steve
如果你不能给女人一辆车就别想
you couldn't have sex with a woman if you gave her a car like that.
所以校长也不让把车开出遛个弯
So he wouldn't even let you take it out for a quick spin?
试开下
A little shakedown cruise?
我不需要他的允许就可以把我的车弄出来
I don't need Shiverson's permission to take my own car out.
管理员的钥匙 就在他桌子上
Valet key. It was on his desk.
[我从未到过这里]
[Music]I've never been here before [music]
[不知道去哪儿 从未遇见你]
[Music]Didn't know where to go Never met you before [music]
[从未去过你家]
- [Music]I've never been to your home [music] - [Tires Squealing]
呼呼
- - [Whooping]
[你可以尝试一切事物]
[Music] You can do all the things that you learn to do [music]
[所有新鲜的事物]
[Music]All around on the ground Pick a part that's new [music]
[你可以做任何你喜欢的事情]
[Music] You can do all the things that you like to do [music]
[所有的 颠倒的事情]
[Music]All around,upside down [music]
-我被她要挟了 -哈 才不是呢
- I swear I'm bein' blackmailed into this. - Ha. Not true.
最好有人来这里拿把刀追着我
Somebody else better be up there takin' the knife after me.
快去刻字吧
Just do it already.
我能让你帮个大忙吗
-  Can I ask you a really big favor?
我今晚有个约会
I have a date tonight.
但这是我的毕业之夜 -我知道
- It's my graduation night. - I know.
抱歉 我忘记快轮到我了
I'm sorry. I forgot that I was closing
我问过妈了 但她张罗派对
I would ask Mom,but she's baby-sitting Patty.
求你了 Sam
Please,Sam?
帮我替下班 算我欠你的
Finish my shift for me. I promise you I will owe you so big-time.
你已经欠我不止一次了
You already owe me your firstborn.
她交给你了 不管怎样 她还是比较喜欢你
Oh,well,you can have her. She likes you better anyway.
轮到你了 傻蛋 那要不要我去刻上我们的名
- Your turn,sucker. - So,do I carve it up?
我得先帮姐顶班 她从来不会帮我顶
I have to do my sister a giant favor that she'd never do for me.
哦 得了吧 我会帮你的啦
Oh,come on. I do you favors.
她像是一年都没有约会过似的
She hasn't had a date in like a year.
好的
All right.
你们看 我们该做什么呢 Kelly
Look,what are we doin',Kelley?
你们饿了吗 - 干嘛 你想死啊
- You guys hungry? - What,do you have a death wish?
Putties一家讨厌我们 -我们能走吗
- The Putties hate our guts. - Can we just leave?
走 去吃点东西
Let's eat.
他在这里做什么
What the hell's he doing in?
你们想来点什么
So,what'll it be?
除了菜单 这里有什么好吃的
Uh,what's good here? Besides the help.
你可以看菜单吗
Can I take your order?
好
Yeah.
你们真的自己做冰淇淋吗
Do you really make your own ice cream?
当然是我们自己亲手手做的
With our very own hands.
那你们到底是怎么做冰淇淋的
How does one actually make ice cream?
这是祖传秘方
It's a secret family recipe.
这你都不愿意告诉我 -你也不例外
- You won't even tell me? - Not even you.
我打赌我能把它弄走 -还真没人成功过呢
- I bet I can get it out of you. - Better men have tried.
这说明那些人不比我优秀
They don't look like better men to me.
3份香草奶昔就行 Kelly 我帮你点了
Three vanilla shakes will be fine. Let me get that for you,Kelley.
如果我转身时你敢盯着我屁股
If you check out my ass when I walk away,
小心你的奶昔会溅你一身
your shake will be in your lap.
我们还是走吧
Let's just get out of here.
你在挑衅我吗 土豪
Are you trying to get at me,Richie?
土豪?-是啊 土豪 有钱人这不是你的名吗
- "Richie"? - Yeah. Richie Rich. That's your name,isn't it?
我们走吧 不不不 他是对的
Let's just get outta here. No,he's right.
你可以从外表上看出很多东西
You can tell a lot from appearances.
看看他
Look at him.
我会说你是个穷鬼
I would say that you're poor.
他们不是流浪汉但却是个穷光蛋
They're not homeless or anything,just run of the mill poor.
看你笑起来的那副德行
Judging from your lazy grin,
估计你也没多聪明
I'd say you're not too bright either.
Kelly 我们走吧
Kell,let's just go.
嘿别闹  暴力 就是穷鬼的挡箭牌
- Take it easy! - Violence. The first refuge of the poor and...
嘿 别打了
Hey,cut it out!
你想受伤还是怎样
- Hey,you want to get yourself hurt,or what?
-谁会伤到我 就凭他吗
Who's gonna hurt me? Him?
啊
Huh?
滚出去 我们走吧 Kelly
- Get out! - Kell,let's just go,man.
-以后算账 小土豪 -你也给我记住了
- Later,Richie. - You can count on it.
你没被赶出去就不错了 他在挑逗你 我实在
- You're lucky I don't kick you out. - He was all over you,and l...
我已经搞定他了 你只是在无事生非
You were just picking a fight while I'm in charge.
都不想跟你讲话了
I can't even talk to you.
Sam.
Kelley 我们走啦 我们还杵在这干什么
Let's just go,Kelley. What are we doin' here,man?
嘿 在走之前我想确认一件事-有屁快放
- Hey,I wanna know one thing before I go. - What's that?
有什么事能更让你抓狂呢 是被你的女人罩着
What freaks you out more? Gettin' bailed out by your girlfriend...
还是她把我当成梦中情人呢
or knowing that she was adding me to her fantasy file?
他说了啥
What did he say?
我想他在说 来爆我菊吧
I think he just said,"Come kick my ass."
哈哈 太爽了 老兄
Hell,that was awesome,man.
你真该看看他表情
You should've seen their faces.
难道不该看你的吗 你个胆小鬼
Should've seen your face,man! You were scared shitless.
没骗你 你真替我出口气了
No lie. You make me feel better about...
-哦 上帝-该死
- Oh,my God. - Holy shit.
嘿 土豪 有本事追我们啊
Hey,Richie. Come and get it.
省省吧 乡巴佬
Come on,farm boy.
- 耶 - 超过他们 搞死他们
- Yeah! - Push it down. Get 'em!
我该提醒你
I should remind you.
前面路段每小时别超过50英里
not to go over 50 miles per hour for the first thousand miles.
闭嘴 Charlie
Shut up,Charlie.
这车有装空气袋么  闭嘴 Charlie
- Are there any air bags back here? - Shut up,Charlie!
嗨 二逼
Hi,pussies.
这可不好玩 我不喜欢这样
This isn't fun. I'm not having fun.
你在干嘛啊
What are you doing?
这就是我要说的啦
That's what I'm talkin' about!
干掉他-他在追尾
- Punch it! -  He's right behind you.
Samantha.
我们有些问题要在警察局问你
We're gonna have a few questions at the station
转过身去上车
so get in the back of the car.
小心你的脑袋
Watch your heads.
你应该去医院检查一下
You should probably come down to the hospital and get checked out.
用不着 我没事
Really,I'm fine.
你知道我是谁吗 小子
You know who I am,son?
Cavanaugh警长
Sheriff Cavanaugh?
我妻子是Jo Cavanaugh
My wife is Jo Cavanaugh,
她的妈妈是Mable（与餐馆同名）
and her mother was Mable.
你今晚差点让我失去女儿
You almost took my daughter from me tonight.
我注意你很多次了
So,you rise me one more time
这次对你更印象深刻
this shit heap you're in is just gonna get deeper.
警长 如果你这是在威胁我的话
Sheriff,if this is a threat...
搞什么飞机
- What the hell is goin' on?
警察的好处就是你不必威胁谁
The nice thing about my job is I don't have to threaten anybody.
把他们也抓起来
Grab them too.
嘿我可是被绑架的啊
Me? Hey,I was practically kidnapped!
法官大人 我知道您是从纽约来的
I understand you're from New York,Your Honor.
土生土长 我也是在上东区的
- Born and bred. - Me too. Upper East Side.
好的很
Good for you.
可惜在这里我们没任何联系 所以别想太多了
But we're not bonding here,so don't get your dress over your head.
我猜你是Morse先生吧 好
Mr. Morse,I presume. Good.
法官大人
Your Honor.
我们觉得假释会不会合适些
we were thinking that some sort of probation would be appropriate.
啊哈 假释 让我们想想看
Probation,huh? Let's think it through.
与其麻烦地每年甚至每星期跟假释官接洽
They talk to a probation officer once a week for a year or so.
还不如连续在社区
Maybe do a couple hundred hours
做几百个小时的志愿者工作
of volunteer work at a community center.
你怎么想的
That what you had in mind?
-保释就行 -不可能 谢谢参与
- Something like that,yes. - Not gonna happen,but thanks for playin'.
先生们 我不知道你们的律师是怎么说的
Gentlemen,I don't know what your lawyers told you,
但事情的性质很严重
but this is pretty serious stuff.
对其他人可以保释
A probation walk was fine for the other boys
那些跟你们一辆车的男孩子们
the ones in the cars with you,
但你们两是主犯
but you two were the cowboys behind the wheel.
我们要对你们采取不同的惩罚手段
We're gonna have to do something different with you.
Arnold先生已准备重建Mable餐厅
I understand Mr. Arnold has been contracted to rebuild Mable's.
是的 法官大人
Yes,that's right,Your Honor.
如果法庭允许的话 我们有一些提议
We'd like to make another suggestion,with the court's permission.
说 Morse先生愿意承担
- Shoot. - Mr. Morse has graciously offered to pay...
重建餐馆的费用 只要撤销对他儿子的指控
for the restaurant,as long as all charges against his son are dropped.
听起来不错哈 我们认为这样比较合适
- That sounds nice,huh? - We thought it appropriate.
但在我的法庭 你要为你犯下的事负责
Not in my court. In my court,you fix what you broke.
完的话 我会撤销这件案子的所有指控
So here it is. I'd be willing to dismiss all charges in this case...
只要这些男孩子志愿去社区服务
if the boys volunteer for community service...
一起重建Mable's Table餐馆
working with the crew rebuilding Mable's Table.
是个你们弥补过失的机会
It's a chance to put back what you took,
如果可能的话 当然 只是如果
and maybe,just maybe,
你们不仅能重建好餐馆
it'll not only result in the building of a restaurant,
还能重塑你们的人格
but in the building of character as well.
你们现在可以与你们的律师谈一谈
You can have some time to talk it over with your attorneys.
没问题 法官 我们都同意
That's okay,Judge. We'll take the deal.
法官 这对Calvin不合适
Your Honor,that's completely impractical for Calvin
你让他住哪
Where would he live?
即Rallston愿意收留他  可宿舍暑假不开放
Even if Rallston would take him,the dorms are closed for the summer.
最近的汽车旅馆到这里也有30英里的路程
The nearest motel is 30 miles away,Your Honor,
他的驾照也被吊销了
and his driver's license has been revoked.
事实上 我们车库楼上有个房间
Actually,we have a room above our garage.
他可以付房租
The boy could pay rent.
我觉得可以  你呢 律师
It works for me. How about you,Counselor?
我们也可以接受 法官大人
That's acceptable to us as well,Your Honor.
又个给Cavanaugh 家惹事的Rallston男孩
Another Rallston boy takes a bite out of the Cavanaugh family.
我跟这件事没关系 说实话 我都不在场
I had nothing to do with this one. I wasn't even here. Exactly.
你...我没责怪任何人
You... Nobody's blaming anybody.
如果你一开始给我打电话就好了
It would have been nice if one of you'd called me
在刚出问题的时候
when the trouble first started.
Jesse跟Alice是在这里刻的字
I remember when Jesse and Alice carved this.
妈 还记得你跟我说过很多次吗
Mom,remember what you said to me so many times?
留得青山在 不怕没柴烧 对吧
As long as we're all alive,it's nothing more than a bad day. Right?
对呀 这一切都会过去的
Yeah. We can beat a bad day. Right?
唉 对啊
Right.
他们来了!他们来了!
They're here! They're here!
那是因为他对我们的出价不满意
That's because he doesn't like the percentage we're offering.
他得想出好点的主意才行
Then he's gonna have to come up with a better deal.
这很关键 对 我得挂了
It's a matter... Yeah. I gotta go.
听着 我跟交代了所有事情 包括你的午餐
Listen,I worked everything out with these people,including your meals.
你就只需要些零花钱
So all you're gonna need is some spending money.
这些够撑一段时间了 如果不够的话
This should last you for a while,but if you need some more,
就打我办公室的电话
you just call my office.
后面几星期你可能很难见到我 嗯
- I'm gonna be a little hard to reach for the next few weeks. - Okay.
嗨 你们好啊 -下午好
- Hello there. - Good afternoon.
我来不及了了 还要赶一架航班
Hey. I'm running a little late,and I have a flight to catch,
我想应该没什么问题了吧
so I assume there's nothing else we need to discuss.
我们没问题了
No. I think we're good..
如果想参观的话 你房间在车库楼上右侧
Your room's right above the garage if you want to go up.
记住我的话
Now,you remember what I told you..
把重心放在有意义的事情上
Keep your eyes forward on the important things.
我知道了
Yes,sir.
它叫Ralph.
That's Ralph.
它也住这里
He lives here too.
真是好极了
Perfect.
要不要我给他送点上去
Maybe I should take him up a plate.
我们都喂到嘴边了 他饿了会下来吃的
Honey,we offered. When he gets hungry,he'll come down.
做了那么多缺德事 让他饿死算了
Let him starve. After everything he did.
当时到底是几辆车在乱跑
How many cars were in that race,anyway?
- 两辆 - 难道他一个人骑两辆吗
- Two. - Was he driving both of them?
我觉得他挺帅的
I think he's hot.
我爹准备让我修篱笆桩修到90岁
My dad's already got me fixing fence posts till I'm 90.
包括重建Mable
Plus the work at Mable's..
就算你不生我的气 我的麻烦也够多的了
I got enough problems without you being mad at me.
我只是觉得你可以更大方些的 仅此而已
I just think you could have been the bigger man. That's all.
好吧
All right. Okay.
那 我们之间没什么问题了吧
Well. Is everything still okay with us?
天哪 我们几百年没这么干了
God,we haven't done that in about a hundred years.
你从来没有吹好过
You were never very good at that.
哈 这可是我教你的啊
Ah,but I'm the one that taught you.
可只有我掌握了
- I'm the one that mastered it. - [Sputtering]
该起床了 富二代 去给奶牛挤奶去
Time to get up,Richie. Gotta evacuate the cows.
是煤气中毒还是怎么了
Is there a gas leak or something?
挤奶啊
Evacuating.
如果你认为我会碰这些东西 那你就是疯了
You're out of your mind if you think I'm touchin' that thing.
早上好
Well,good morning.
- 要吃什么吗 早务后有早餐
- Can I fix you something? - Breakfast is served after morning chores.
我不吃早餐
I don't eat breakfast
我只是想知道我们什么时候去干活
I was just coming in to find out when we leave for work.
20分钟后到卡车那去
Be at the truck in 20 minutes.
-你不累吗富二代  -不
- Not getting tired,are you,Richie? - No.
在你爱抚那些奶牛时我去补了一个小时的觉
Got an extra hour's sleep while you were fondling your cows.
午餐好了
[Mr. Arnold] That's lunch!
伙计们 休息时间 吃的跟饮料在冷藏室里
Break time,guys. Food and drink's in the cooler.
我自己有午饭吃
I'll get my own lunch.
随便你  午饭啊 一起去吃吧
Suit yourself. Lunch! Let's go.
好吧 我走了
Okay,I'm outta here.
当你爸真好
-  - Good to be your father.
当你女儿真好
Good to be your daughter.
妈 你知道我昨晚在想什么吗
- Do you know what I was thinking about last night,Mom? - What?
他们会给我们钱重建对吧
They're giving us all this money to rebuild. Right?
我们可以从头开始 好好玩玩
So we can start all over from scratch and have fun.
我们可以去古董店
We can go to antique stores...
或者是跳蚤市场弄些时髦的家具
and flea markets and get funky furniture.
可以啊 去Falco医生那里后再去
We could do that. We could stop on the way back from Dr. Falco's.
我都忘了这件事了
I completely forgot about Dr. Falco.
这是个好迹象 我想你的膝盖应该好多了
That's a good sign. I guess your knee hasn't been bothering you.
妈 我的膝盖很好
Mom,my knee's fine.
那我能取消预约吗 -不行
- So can I cancel Dr. Falco? - No.
真讨厌 -我知道
- Oh,I hate this. - I know.
他只是想确认你真的完全康复了
He's just making sure everything's still okay.
我的膝盖没事 为什么我们老是来这里啊
My knee's fine. Why do we have to keep coming here?
- 这是医生的要求 -Samantha
- Because the doctor said so. - Samantha?
当一些事物从我们身边被夺走
When something is taken away from us so violently,
就像是发生在Mable餐厅的火灾
like the recent fire at Mable's Table,
我们不禁要扪心自问
we are forced to ask questions.
这仅仅只是个糟糕的事件吗
Was it simply a terrible accident?
就像是两个原子之间任意的碰撞
Atoms colliding at random?
究竟是是年轻人做出了错误选择的结果
A result of young people making poor choices?
还是因为这是上帝…
Or was it the hand of God...
他给我们制定的人生大计划中的一小部分
a part of a larger plan that He might have for us?
Jasper你基友Kelly今天去哪了
Hey,Jasper. Where's your new pal Kelley today?
哦他在你房间里 跟你老妈搞着呢
Oh,he's at your house,getting busy with your mom.
是吗 昨晚我跟你妈一起
Really? 'Cause last night when I was with your mom.
你妈还说他可爱
,she said he was kind of cute.
-我快嫉妒疯了-别说了
It made me jealous. Enough with the mother thing already.
- 我同意 - 不好意思
- I second that. - Excuse me.
我受够了这些话题了 我还蛮喜欢你妈妈的
What? I'm just saying enough's enough. I like your mom.
各位 我们今晚要去裸泳 想去吗
Hey,guys. We're goin' skinny dipping tonight. Wanna come?
我爸让我工作呢 我的男人不穿衣服时可帅了
- Dad's making me work. - My man looks good naked.
是啊 我喜欢人猿泰山
- - Yeah,I'm like Tarzan.
-一会见好吗 -嗯哼
- See you later? - Mm-hmm.
下午好 各位同学 嘉宾们
Good afternoon,classmates and invited guests.
今天我们要给我们的幼儿时代
Today we mark the end of our infancy,
我们的童年
the end of our childhood,
我们的开始画上句号
the end of our beginning.
作为毕业生 我们满怀希望期待未来
As new graduates we look forward with hope to the future,
不久后未来也变成了过去
and then the future becomes the past.
我们生活有意义吗
At what point in our lives
有思考过我们的过去及未来吗
do we begin thinking about the past and the future?
当我还是个孩子的时候 我没怎么考虑过这些
I know when I was a child I never gave them much thought.
我想念那些日子
I miss those days.
Robert Frost 美国诗人
Robert Frost曾写过他那无忧无虑的童年
Robert Frost once wrote about his carefree youth
爬过的桦树干
,climbing the branches of birch trees.
他写道 我过去就是这样一个荡树的孩子
He wrote,"So I was once myself a swinger of birches,
而现在我总是梦想着回到过去
and so I dream of going back to be."
我也是 Frost先生
So do I,Mr. Frost.
我也想回到过去
So do I.
去吃饭吧 你准备好没
Let's go. You ready?
我不饿
I'm not hungry.
我们快准备好了
We'll be right up.
你不觉得这些家人对你很友好吗
These folks are being very gracious,don't you think?
在那么发生多事情后还让你到他们家住
Inviting you to their home after everything that's happened.
拜托 我是来工作的 我有活要干
Look. I come to work. I do my job. Okay?
我就答应做这些而已 我的保释书上可没写
That's the deal I made. My probation doesn't say anything...
要我必须跟他们排排坐吃果果
about me sittin' around spittin' out watermelon seeds with you people.
我敢说 孩子
I gotta tell you,son.
以你这种心态在这里熬不过一个暑假
I don't think you're gonna make the summer with this attitude.
我又不是你孩子
I'm not your son.
对 你不是
No,you're not.
爷爷 - 嘿
- Grandpa! - Hey.
噢哦 我的孙女好吗 太想念这里的午餐了
- Whoa. How's my girl? - Earl,missin' a great lunch here.
来把她给我抱吧 -我们这里吃的多得是
- I'll catch up. - We have tons of food,baby.
Jo 很感激你们提供这些食物 谢谢你们
Jo,appreciate this. Thank you.
你们工作那么幸苦 这是应该的
You guys have been working so hard,you deserve it.
Sam去哪了
Where's Sam?
别担心 我不会告诉其他人你吃过了
Don't worry,I won't tell anybody you actually ate.
你别总是那副不高兴的样子
I'd like it if you'd stop sulking long enough to try.
- 我没有不高兴 - 别抵赖了
- I'm not sulking. - Oh,come on.
我们请你过去吃午餐
We invite you over for lunch.
你就像个大孩子一样坐在这里
And you decide to sit out here like a really big baby.
因为我给你这种印象
And at what point did I give you the impression
所以你就可以跑来这羞辱我了吗
that it was okay to come out here and insult me?
离Samantha远点
Stay away from Samantha.
放轻松 我没有对你女朋友下手
Relax. I'm not makin' a move on your girlfriend.
-你认为我担心的是这个-不知道 不关心
- You think I'm worried about that? - Don't know,don't care.
离她远点
Stay away from her.
哦 那你又想怎样
Or what,exactly?
听着 富二代 别把我惹毛了 知道吗
Listen,Richie. You don't want to mess with me. All right?
哦哦 好怕怕
Ooh. Scary.
真是惊讶,你还担心女朋友啊
I'm surprised you even bother with a girlfriend
看你对付那些母牛那么有一手
you got such a good thing with those cows.
你什么意思  哦 承认吧
- What's that supposed to mean? - Aw,come on.
你在那牛圈里妻妾成群
You got yourself a regular harem out there.
每天早上掀开她们的裙子
Get your hands up their skirt every morning.
晚上给她们唱着小曲
You serenade them every night.
你该不是爱上那些600磅的反刍动物了吧
That,or you're in love with a 600-pounder who likes to chew her vomit.
你知道我在那做什么吗 -做什么
- You know what I'm really doin' up there,Richie? - What's that?
做你老妈
Your mother.
你怎么回事啊 老兄
What's your problem,man?
嘿!嘿!
Hey! Hey!
别打了 你到底怎么了
Stop it! What's the matter with you?
行了 站起来 我们走吧
Come on. Get up. Let's go. Let's go.
嘿嘿 你别闹了
Hey,hey! You can quit right now.
给我住手
Right now.
我不干了
I quit.
你不能退出 这不是工作 这是判决 见鬼
You can't quit. It isn't a job. It's a sentence! God.
-让我跟那孩子谈 - 不 不
- I'll talk with that kid. - No,no! Earl.
先等等 让他走 让他冷静一下
Just wait. Let him go. Let him cool off,okay?
你看着我 你知道该怎么做
You. Look at me. You know better.
现在去卡车那里
Go to the truck. Now.
Albert 你下周二要懂得这段弹奏好吗
Albert. I expect you to know that piece by next Tuesday. Okay.
-好的 - 好 你可以走了
- Okay. - Okay. Get outta here.
来坐下
Come and sit.
老爸已经教训过我了 所以
Dad already gave me an earful,so,uh...
你还记得怎么弹吗
You still remember how to play?
音乐一直都是属于我们的 对吧
Music's always been our thing,hasn't it?
你和我
You and me?
它一直是我们属于我们的
It'll always be something we share.
我猜你觉得Kelly真的很幸运
I imagine you think Kelley's real lucky.
家里那么有钱
Gets to have all that money.
看起来拥有了全世界
Seems to have the whole world in his hands.
你有没有想过自己很幸福呢
Ever consider maybe you're the lucky one?
在法庭上我都没有看到他妈妈
I didn't see a mother in that courtroom.
你杀了它
- - You killed him.
杀了谁 你到底在讲什么
Killed who? What are you talkin' about?
你就直接把他扔垃圾箱了
You just threw him in the garbage!
他对你做了什么你要这样-你说那只老鼠吗
- What did he ever do to you? - Are we talkin' about the mouse?
你这个混蛋 我再也不想跟你讲话了
You're just a jerk. I'm never speaking to you again.
我无法忍受这附近了 连件漂亮衣服都买不着
I'm just so sick of not being able to buy good clothes around here.
你下星期想不想去波士顿
So,you want to come to Boston next week?
我很热
I'm hot.
我想喝些东西
I need to go get something to drink.
我姐姐不喜欢你
My sister hates you.
为什么 她都不了解我
Why? She doesn't even know me.
好吧 她讨厌你是出于原则上的
Well,she hates you on principle.
我很高兴不是针对个人的
I'm glad it's not personal.
这又是怎么了
What was that about?
我杀死了Ralph
I killed Ralph.
哦应该把你逮捕起来
Oh. You could get arrested for that.
有手铐么
Will there be handcuffs?
你想被拷起来
Do you want handcuffs?
那要看拷我的人是谁咯
Depends on who's puttin' them on.
可能是警长哦 所以别高兴的太早了
Probably the sheriff,so don't get too excited.
你约会时还带着警长吗
Do you always bring the sheriff on dates?
只要我没犯法就用不着了
Not if I'm the one who's breaking the law.
今天晚上来找我
Meet me tonight.
看你能得多少分 射门手
Let's see what you got,slugger.
好的
Okay.
哦 击中一球了
Oh,there's a shot!
本垒打 - 那才不是我最好的一垒
- It's a home run! - That wasn't my best pitch.
- 其实棒球不是我的菜 -那是
- Baseball's not really my sport. - What is?
- 田径 - 不是吧
- Track. - Really?
跨栏 我以前挺擅长的 但是现在
Running hurdles. I was pretty good,but then...
把你的膝盖摔碎后这一切很快都改变了
cracking your kneecap will change that one in a hurry.
真可惜
Ouch. Yeah.
以前还得过波士顿大学的全额奖学金
I had a full ride to B.U.
现在只能用老方法去支付大学费用
So I'll just have to pay for college the old-fashioned way now.
像学生贷款
Student loans.
大学后呢
What's after college?
也许会学医
Probably med school.
虽然有时候我会有些不实际的想法
Although I'd like to toy with the idea...
像是一辈子就这里的树林里写写诗
of spending my whole life here in the woods,writing poetry.
是啊 学医听起来更实际些
Yeah. Med school sounds a bit more practical.
有些事听起来比在桦树上荡树枝还糟糕
There are worse things to be than a swinger of birches.
你知道那首诗
You know that poem?
我的最爱
My favorite.
我听到你的演说了
I heard your speech.
什么
What?
我看到你在漫步 然后你就跟着我了
I saw you walking. And you followed me?
我喜欢你的演讲 说真的
I liked it. Honest.
虽然那首诗挺让人伤感的 是吧
It's a sad poem too,though,isn't it?
生活是一片迷失的森林
Life is too much like a pathless wood .
让你的脸又痛又痒
where your face burns and tickles.
当你撞上了蜘蛛网
The cobwebs,broken across it.
忽然一只眼又流泪 因为树枝在它睁开抽了它
And one eye is weeping from having a twig lash across.
我更愿意逃离地球一小会儿
I'd like to get away from Earth a while,
然后再回来重新开始
and then come back to it and begin over.
你在想什么
What are you thinking?
我在想
I was just thinking about that .
你那天带给我的那个三明治
ham sandwich you brought me the other day.
好吃吗
What about it?
如果再有芥末酱 或者是
I was just wondering if there was mustard,or...
-刚才感觉很好 - 只是很好吗
- That was nice. - Nice?
很多事情都会变得美好起来-比如说
- There was a lot going on in "nice." - Like what?
- 我该给它起什么名 -他应该叫米奇
- What name should I give him? - His name should be Mikey.
-Mikey Red怎样-不错
- How about Mikey Red? - Mikey Red is a very good name.
妈 这个怎样
Mom. What about this one?
啊 这个还好 没有太大惊喜
Ah,it's okay. It doesn't thrill me.
妈咪 妈咪 我想尿尿
Mom. Mommy,I have to go tinkle.
没事 我带她去
I'll take her. It's all right.
- 多谢了 老妈 - 没事
- Thanks,Mom. - Okay.
你在干嘛 老盯着我看 -哼哼
- What,already? You keep staring at me. - Mm-hmm.
你一直在跟他见面 对不对
You're seeing him,aren't you?
-跟谁 -别跟我装蒜
- Who? - Don't even think about denying it.
我知道这个表情 Sam 我也有过这个表情
I know that look,Sam. I have had that look.
我们就是一起玩玩而已 没什么大不了的
We just hung out. No big deal.
你疯了吗 你了解Rallston的家伙吗
Are you crazy? You know what those Rallston guys are like.
不知道 不过我知道你认识那些是啥样的
- No. I know what your Rallston guy was like. - Excuse me.
相信我  他们都是一个德行
Trust me. They are all the same.
你觉得我不知道你在想什么吗
You don't think I know what you're feeling?
他对你来说刺激 出挑 小危险的诱惑是么
Hmm? He seems exciting to you,different,maybe even a little dangerous.
但是相信我 亲爱的 我经历过这些
Believe me,honey. I have been there.
我又不跟他结婚 简 我们只是 -玩玩而已
- I'm not marrying him,Jen. We're just... - Hanging out.
是吗
Right.
是啊
咦 我们不是过会儿才见面吗
Hey. I thought we were gonna meet later.
好吧 看到你走进来就有些情不自禁了
Well,when I saw you walk in,I couldn't wait.
我跟 Malcolm说我走路回家了
I told Malcolm I was walking home.
你兄弟Pete在这里 - 是啊 我知道
- Your,uh,good buddy Pete's up there. - Yeah,I know.
难道我就不能买瓶汽水吗
So I can't buy a soda?
- 过来 -你想做什么
- Come here. - What are you doing?
嘿 宝贝儿
Hey,baby.
Vanessa 看我发现了什么
Hey,Vanessa. Look what we got here.
-Sam你在做什么 - 没 什么也没做
- Sam,what are you doing? - Nothing. I'm not doing anything.
- 你在背叛我兄弟 -我们走吧 好吗
- You're cheatin' on my boy. - Let's go. Okay?
来吧
Come on.
我不想夹在你跟另一个家伙之间
I don't want to get between you and another guy.
这样太不爽了
That's just not cool.
我知道
I know.
我跟Jasper之间跟以前已经不太一样了
Things are different with me and Jasper now.
我们已经不再是小孩子了
We're not little kids anymore.
有些事是会改变的 对吗
And things change,right?
他知道那些改变吗
Does he know they've changed?
我们现在别讲这些了好吗
Let's not talk about this right now.
我希望我们做一些 Frost说过的那些事
I wish we could do what Frost says.
离开地球一小会儿 然后再回来重新开始
Leave Earth for a while and come back and begin all over.
.那样真好 - 是很好
- It would be so nice. - Nice.
Nice.很美好
Nice.
- 你在做什么- 离开地球一小会儿
- What you doin'? - Getting away for a while.
-这里是佛罗里达 -你说什么是佛罗里达州
- Florida. - What's Florida?
- 你的最南端 -嗯哼
- The southernmost tip of you. - Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯
Mmm.
佛罗里达州好痒啊
Florida tickles.
-我们就一路向北 好吗 -好的
- Then let's move north,shall we? - All right.
到了佐治亚州的桃子林
Got Georgia peaches.
还有南加利福尼亚
And South Carolina.
一个美丽的州
A very beautiful state.
这里是北加利福尼亚
This is North Carolina.
我走得更北了
I move further north,
我发现了马里兰州
and I find Maryland.
嗯嗯
Mmm.
-看起来马里兰州也痒了 -我想是的
- Seems Maryland tickles too. - I think so.
-我想这里是纽约 -嗯
- I suppose that one there's New York. - Mmm.
这里是泽西州 那里是纽约
That's Jersey. That's New York.
要拜访一下吗
Planning a visit?
不了
No.
我朝着马萨诸塞出发
I'm heading towards Massachusetts.
马萨诸塞欢迎你
Massachusetts welcomes you.
有多糟糕
How bad is it?
能修好吗
Is it fixable?
我不知道 挺严重的
I don't know. It's pretty bad.
我猜你跟Pete谈过了
Guess you spoke to Pete.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我不知道
I don't know.
那个家伙走进这个小镇 说了一些话
This guy walks into town,and he says a few things,
会让你产生幻想
and he makes you think a few things.
但那些都不是真实的 我们才是真实的
But it's not real. We're real.
我跟你 我们才是真爱
Me and you. We've always been real.
我知道我们终究会在一起的
I've always known that we're gonna be together.
我想你也知道
I think you have too.
-如果仅仅是这个的话  -不 别这样
- Well,what if the only reason that... - No. Come on.
别这么对我
Don't do this.
我们下星期有个7月4号舞会
We have a Fourth of July dance coming up next week.
在牡蛎烧烤店旁边的沙滩集会
Clam bake,camping on the beach.
还记得吗 就像是去年一样 跟我一起来吧
The whole thing. Just like last year. Remember? Come with me.
我是说
I mean
你跟他在一起有什么结果 你知道吧
this thing with him is just gonna turn out to be a thing. You know?
你不会让我们之间毁在那些事上的 对吧
You don't want to waste us on that,do you?
哦 哇
Ohh,wow.
这真是太美了
This is beautiful!
我最喜欢的地方
My favorite spot.
嗯 不管怎样 7月4号有一场舞会
So,anyway,there's this Fourth of July dance.
你知道吗 镇上的人都会去 这是传统
And,you know,the whole town goes. It's this tradition.
到时会有烟花 食物
And they have fireworks and food...
人们还会带着他们心仪的对象等等……
and people bring their dates and stuff.
Samantha 我很荣幸能与你一起去
Hey,Samantha. I would be honored to be your date.
哇哦 天哪
Wow. Gosh.
额 只是我有点
Uh... Just that I sort of...
我可能得跟Jasper一起去
I kind of have to go with Jasper.
我不觉得你跟他还
I didn't think things with you and him were...
我不知道我跟他是否还是以前那样 -我知道
- I don't know what they are. - I see.
你对他还有感觉吗
Do you still have feelings for him?
嗯 当然 我对他一直都有感觉 但是
Well,of course. I always will,but...
我不是 我的意思是 这个
I'm not... I mean,it's...
-但不是非常地 -Samantha 我不懂
- not really... - Um,Samantha,I don't understand.
我是说 我们俩这算什么
I mean,what are you doing with me?
你对我来说只是个意外罢了 你知道的
You've just kind of taken me by surprise,you know.
我对你没那个意思
L... I didn't expect you.
你看 舞会后我们也许可以在一起
Look,maybe we can get together after the dance.
我 我不能 因为我们还要去鳕鱼岬
I,uh... I can't because we're going to Cape Cod.
而且 而且我们每年都去鳕鱼岬的
A-And we... We go to Cape Cod every year.
那也没关系 别担心了
Like,don't worry about it. I mean,
又不是什么大不了的事
It's not like we got some serious thing.
你知道的 我是说 就是一起玩玩而已 对吗
You know,I mean,we're just havin'fun,right?
对啊
Right.
你好 是的 我是Samantha.
Hello. Yes,this is Samantha.
嗨
Hi.
好的 那他怎么说的
Well,did he say what it was about?
好的
Okay.
好的 我星期二会告诉他们的
Sure,I'll tell them Tuesday.
再见
Bye.
谁打来的
-Who was on the phone?
- 就是些搞推销的 - 哦 多讨厌啊
- Somebody selling something. - Oh,don't you hate that?
是啊
Yeah.
你也可以管它叫"Ralph."
Thought you could call him "Ralph."
我在康科德楼上的一间宠物商店发现他的
I found him at a pet store up in Concord.
你不觉得他很酷吗
He's pretty cool,don't you think?
我想他挺不错的
He's okay,I guess.
那让你们俩熟悉熟悉吧
I'll let you two get acquainted.
嗨 Ralph Jr
Hey,Ralph,Jr.
嘿 Jas 快上车
Hey,Jas,come on!
怎么了 富二代 没有人愿意跟你一起吗
What's wrong,Richie,you couldn't find a date?
Jas!
- Jas!
- 嘿 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
[我离开沙发]
[Woman] [Music]I left my couch and like [music]
[哭得像个孩子]
[Music]A crying child [music]
[锁上身后的门]
[Music]Locked the doors behind me [music]
[把痛苦存档]
[Music]Put the pain on file [music]
[像窗子一样破碎]
[Music]Broken like a window [music]
[我知道我迷失了双眼]
[Music]I see my blindness now [music]
[我需要爱]
[Music]And I need love [music]
[那不是些多伤感的监狱]
[Music]Not some sentimental prison [music]
[我需要爱]
[Music]I need love [music]
我等不及去买下这件游泳衣了
[music][Continues] I can't wait. Bought this new bathing suit.
这是连体的 不过中间有些丝网
It's a one-piece,but it's mesh in the middle.
天哪 那件真是太酷了
Oh,my God. It's so wicked cool.
我法说清楚 你得看看 它是深黑色
I can't explain it. You got to see it. It's black,and it's deep dyed.
[像窗子一样破碎]
[Music]Broken like a window [music]
[我知道我迷失了双眼]
[Music]I see my blindness now [music]
[我需要爱]
[Music]And I need love [music]
[那不是伤感的监狱]
[Music]Not some sentimental prison [music]
[我需要爱]
[Music]I need love [music]
这个活动只允许这个镇的居民去的 对吧
Now,it's for members of the town,right?
既然 我荣幸成为这个镇
And since I... am now a proud member...
的一员 我就可以去 对吧
of this town,then I should be allowed to go,right?
我应该去 我绝对可以去
I should definitely go. I should absolutely be allowed.
就这么定了 我可是个出色的舞者
It's settled then. I am a great dancer.
[我需要爱]
[Music]I need love [music]
[那不是伤感的监狱]
[Music]Not some sentimental prison [music]
[我需要爱]
[Music]I need love [music]
你们谁 谁想跟我去的 啊
Who here... wants to be my date? Huh?
你想 跳舞吗
Do you... wanna dance?
噢 宝贝儿 你愿意跟我跳舞吗
Come on,baby. Will you go to the dance with me?
那好 好 好的
All right. Okay. Fine.
- 要给你的女仆小费哦
- Be sure to tip your waitress.
拜拜
Adieu.
-不要 我不喜欢那顶帽子 -看上去很合你
- No. No,I hate that hat. -  You look great.
这顶帽子不错
It's a good hat.
嘿 怎么了
Hey,what's up?
嗨 Kelly-嘿 Kelly
- Hey,Kelley. - Hey,Kelley.
你醉了吗 -没有哇
- Are you drunk? - No.
-干嘛这么问 你呢 -我没醉
- No. Why,are you? - No.
-老兄 你最好走开 - 走开
- Man,maybe you'd better go,huh? - Go?
拜托 我才刚来
Hey,I just got here. Huh?
- Kelly 你该走了 - 走 为什么
- Kelley,I think that you should leave. - Leave? Why?
哦 这个乡巴佬要咆哮了吗
Oh,farm boy's getting ready to rumble,huh?
来嘛 跟我跳个舞
Come on. Come on,dance with me.
Jasper 你不介意吧
Huh? Jasper doesn't mind,do you,Jasper?
- 在我揍你前最好滚蛋 知道吗 -嘿 嘿
- I think you better go,before I kick... All right? - Hey. Hey.
干嘛每个人都怒发冲冠的啊
Hey,what's everybody getting so huffy for,huh?
放轻松
Huh? Relax.
就跟你跳会舞嘛
Hey,gonna dance with you. [Muttering]
来啊
Come on.
-你要去哪 -回波士顿
- Where you going? - Back to Boston.
那你的假释怎么办
What about your probation?
你本来可以跟我跳个舞的
You could've just danced with me.
-我在那里有约会了 -应该是我跟你的约会的
- I was there with a date. - I should've been your date!
我想我跟你解释过了
I thought that I explained that to you.
对啊 你已经做出了你的选择
Yeah,you made your choice.
Kelley 那不公平
Kelley,that's not fair.
-跟我走吧 -什么
- Look,come with me. - What?
-去波士顿 -我不能跟你去波士顿
- Come to Boston. - I can't go with you to Boston.
就一个周末 你可以星期天回来
Just for the weekend. You can be back by Sunday.
Samantha 我们不必躲躲藏藏的
Look,Samantha. We don't have to hide.
我们可以正大光明在一起
We can be together.
怎么了 Sam
What's goin' on?
Sam
Sam?
你跟他说什么了
What did you say to him?
我不能……
I can't go...
跟你走 Jasper
with you,Jasper.
什么
What?
-我不能跟你在一起 -什么 不 别这样说
- I can't be with you. - What? No... Stop sayin' that.
只要 跟我一起走 好吗
Just... Just come with me,okay?
我们本应在一起
Me and you were supposed to be together.
我只是不敢确定了
I just don't know anymore.
没有人比我更懂你 对吗
N-Nobody knows you like I do,all right?
没有人比我更了解你
Nobody... Nobody sees you like I do.
我们属于彼此
We belong together.
我们……
We...
我爱你 我 我爱你 Sam
I love you. L-l-I love you,Sam.
我要走了
I have to go.
对不起
I'm sorry.
[神圣完美的酮体]
[Music]Figure of divine perfection [music]
[没有人带着更多的仰慕去爱着它]
[Music]No one's loved with more affection [music]
[我们心有灵犀]
[Music]Soul to soul we breathe [music]
[我不会让命运战胜我]
[Music] Oh,I won't let the fates succeed [music]
[担忧在沉思的时光里]
[Music] Worried hours of contemplation [music]
[喃喃细语]
[Music] Whispered bits of conversation [music]
[思绪井然]
[Music] Unaffected orderlies [music]
[洁净的房间与大厅]
[Music]Disinfected rooms and hallways [music]
[你是否愿意与上帝同眠]
[Music]And if you sleep you sleep with God [music]
[如果我从心底里哭泣]
[Music]And if I cry it's for my heart [music]
[因为你一旦睡去]
[Music] 'Cause if you sleep [music]
[你一旦睡去]
[我也将睡去]
[Music]I'll sleep too [music]
你的管家呢
Where's your butler?
这个嘛
Well,
这周末跟我爸出城了 所以
it's Fourth of July weekend plus my dad's out of town,so...
能带我参观下你的豪宅么
Can you show me around your mansion?
这只是个普通的房子
It's just a house.
就看看嘛 看下厨房还有吃的吗
Come on,let's go see if there's food in the kitchen.
要不然
How 'bout...
我就
I take the tour...
自己看去！
myself!
马 可
Marco.
波 罗
Polo.
马 可
Marco.
波 罗
Polo.
嘿 Samantha
Hey,Samantha?
Samantha 别闹了
Samantha,come on.
游戏结束
Game's over.
.Samantha出来 -怎么了嘛
- Samantha,get out of the tub. - What's the matter?
马上从浴缸里出来
Just get out of the tub.
Kelly 怎么了
Kelley,what's wrong?
Kelly……
Kelley...
你没事吧
You okay?
我母亲很爱她的玫瑰
My mother loved her roses.
她可以坐在这里几个小时
She would just sit in here for hours .
嗅着玫瑰发呆
and stare at 'em,breathin' 'em in.
它们每年只在盛夏之末盛开 但是
They only bloom once a year at the end of summer,but...
母亲总是说这是玫瑰的独特之处
she always said that's what made 'em so special.
虽然不久后它们便凋谢了
And then just fade away.
那个夏天我还是个孩子
In the summers when I was a kid,
她经常带着我站在雨中
she used to take me outside to stand in the rain.
她说这对头发有好处
She said it was good for our hair.
她有一头娟秀的长发
Hers was so long.
如此美丽的长发
So beautiful.
最后我发现她躺在在浴缸里
I found her in the tub.
水里淌满了鲜血 像是一幅油画
The water was so thick with blood,it looked like paint.
我试着用毛巾去包住她的手腕 想要止住鲜血
I tried to wrap a towel around her wrist to stop the bleeding.
但她已经不再流血了
But she wasn't bleeding.
浴缸里全是她的鲜血
It was all in the tub.
我知道我母亲一直很忧郁
I always knew my mother was sad,you know?
但她从来没说过什么
She didn't say a word.
就这么放弃了自己的生命
She just gave up.
我在想有没有躺在床上的世界纪录
I wonder what the world record is for staying in bed.
我打赌我们很容易就打破记录了
I bet we could break it easy.
呆在这里好吗
Stay here?
我去给你弄早餐
I'm gonna make you breakfast.
不是说要打破记录吗
What about the record?
[不管什么背离你抛弃我]
[Woman] [Music] Whatever turns you on turns me on [music]
[让我们开始吧 是的没错]
[Music] Oh,let's get started Ohh,that's right [music]
[不管什么背离你抛弃我]
[Music] Whatever turns you on turns me on [music]
[宝贝 我就在这]
[Music] Oh,baby,I'm there [music]
[我不害怕]
[Music]I ain't scared [music]
[我们旋转不息 翻天覆地]
[Music] We're spinnin'round and round and upside down [music]
[从左到右自由飞翔 别摧毁了飞行器]
[Music]Flyin' left and right Don't crash this flight [music]
[在南北之间 发现只有自己在翱翔]
[Music]From north and south I'm all I found [music]
[不管什么背离你抛弃我]
[Music] Whatever turns you on turns me on [music]
[让我们开始吧]
- [Music] Oh,let's get started [music] - [Footsteps]
不是说让你躺在床上吗
I thought I told you to wait in bed?
我有预感这里可能会有点挤
I have a feeling it might get a little crowded.
我去叫Kelly
I'll get Kelley.
你跟Kelly是怎么认识的
So,how did you and Kelley meet?
-他烧毁了我们家的餐厅 -原来如此
- He burned down my family's restaurant. - Oh.
我不敢相信你居然把女人带进你母亲的房子里
I don't believe you'd bring a woman into Mom's house.
这回你别想把责任推给我
Don't you even think about turning this around on me.
一 这是我的房子 二 现在是你的问题
First of all,this is my house,and this is a discussion about you...
还有你将要继续的糜烂生活
and the fact that you continue to be so reckless with your life.
-那是我的事 -错 你的干每件事都有我的影子
- Dad,it's my life. - No! Everything that you do reflects on me.
你现在马上给我回到Putnam
What you're gonna do now is you're going back to Putnam immediately.
完成你的责任
You will complete your obligation there.
三个周后 你就要进普林斯顿了-为什么
- And in three week's time,you will start at Princeton. - Dad,why?
为什么我要这么早上大学
Why do I have to start early?
为什么不能跟同龄人一起上学吗
Why can't I just start with everybody else?
我千方百计才把你弄进入 你必须去
I had to pull a lot of strings to make this happen,and you're going.
我看那个女孩对你来说是个不小的干扰
Now,I'm sure this girl of yours is a very nice distraction.
也就那么回事 只是个干扰罢了
That's what it is. Just a distraction.
那不是你的生活
It's not your life.
以后你还有更重要的事情
You have much bigger things ahead of you.
该是向前看齐的时候了
Now get your eyes forward,already.
你现在是不是还要赶公车呢
I think you have a bus to catch.
你觉得你自己在干什么
- So what is it you think you're doing?
-你到底在做什么 -我不知道
- What is it that you think I'm doing? - I don't know.
不管你在做什么 该停止了
- But whatever it is,it is gonna stop! - [Phone Ringing]
停止什么 你知道他是什么样的人
- What's gonna stop? - You know what he is!
不 你根本不了解他  你要接电话吗
- No. And you have no idea what he is! - Will you get the phone?
你没从你姐那吸取教训吗 我又不是Jen
- Didn't you learn from your sister? - I'm not Jen.
-我在做之前清楚得很
- I'm walking into this with my eyes open.
-你知道自己在做什么吗
- What is it you're walking into?
跟一个孩子的感情纠葛
A relationship... with this kid?
再过几个星期他就走了
He's gonna be gone in a few weeks.
你将再也不会见到他
You're not gonna hear from him again.
-也许他跟别人不同-说来听听
- Well,maybe he's different. - Tell me how.
-也许他爱着我-他都不懂什么是爱
- Maybe he loves me. - He doesn't know the meaning of the word!
-你不了解他 -Falco医生的电话
- And you don't know him -That was Dr. Falco's office.
-他怎么说的
- What did he want?.
他想要确认你明天的预约
- He wanted to confirm your appointment for tomorrow.
-他们说跟你谈过了 你为什么不告诉我们
- They said they talked to you. Why didn't you tell us?
-因为我不会去
- - 'Cause I'm not going.
为什么 因为我没事 我的膝盖也没事
- Why? - Because I'm fine. And my knee is fine.
一切都很好 而且我不想再谈论了
And it's been fine. And I'm sick of talking about it!
Samantha!
我来找Samantha
I'm looking for Samantha.
我没见到她
I haven't seen her.
那好 如果你见到她的话
Well,if you see her,
就告诉她快点回家
just tell her it's important she come home.
算我求你了 Kelly
Look,I'm asking,Kelley.
好吗
Okay?
一切都还好吗
Is everything okay?
是啊
Yeah.
我喜欢这地方
I love this spot.
就像是地球上的天堂
It's like heaven... right here on earth.
也许天堂就是这样的
Maybe that's what heaven is.
也许有着我们这一生挚爱的人们与地方
Maybe we go through life collecting people and places we love.
就是我们的天堂
And they become our heaven.
你的母亲就在那里
And that's where your mom is.
在天堂里被她所爱的事物围绕着
She's in her heaven surrounded by everything that she loves.
包括你
Including you.
-你这么觉得吗 -是啊
- You think so? - Yeah.
来赛跑吧
Let's race.
Sam...
-Samantha
- Samantha!
怎么了 你没事吧
What happened? Are you okay?
到底怎么了
So,what's the matter?
- Samantha,发生什么了
- Samantha,what is it?
我得告诉你一些事
There's something I have to tell you.
天哪 那是怎么从她的腿转移到肝脏的
Boy,how does it go from her leg to her liver?
骨肉瘤就是这么转移的
That's how osteosarcoma works.
我们一直都知道有这个可能性
We always knew that this was a possibility.
那我们能做什么
What can we do?
我希望还有其他治疗手段能提供给你们
I wish there was a list of options I could give you.
但现在已经没有办法了
but there just isn't.
只是它转移得太快了
It just moved so fast.
Sam.
嗨
Hey.
我出去走走 一会儿回来
I'm gonna go for a walk. I'll be back in a minute.
来 坐在我旁边
Come and sit with me.
Kelley...
当你跟别人说你得了癌症
When you tell someone you have cancer,
不管你怎么说的 他们只是感到很遗憾而已
no matter how you say it,they just end up feeling sorry for you.
但是我不希望你为我感到遗憾
And I didn't want you feeling sorry for me.
你会死吗
Could you die from this?
我会的
I am gonna die from this.
他们没有治疗的办法吗 嗯
- There's... There's nothing that they can do for you? - Sure,
他们还有一些方法可以治疗
there are things they can do.
但那对我来说不合适
They're just not the right things for me.
-但只要能治你的病 -不可能的
- But if they can save you... - Won't.
癌细胞已经转移了
It's already spread.
即使是用他们能提供的最好治疗方法
Even with the treatment,the best they can offer...
我顶多能活一到两年
is a chance I could live a year or two.
太不值得了
It's not worth it.
那又怎样 你就这么放弃了
So,what? You just gonna give up?
你就这么死去吗
You just gonna die?
不
No.
我会活下去
I'm going to live.
不只是你
Just not as long as you.
来看看这些东西
Come look at this stuff.
在 Ridge路的一个老地方看到的
- Found it at an old place out on Ridge Road.
噢 是吗
Oh,yeah.
Jasper,Kelley 来这里
Jasper,Kelley,come here.
-这是英格兰松木 很好很柔软
-This,uh,English pine... nice and soft.
看看 这个用来刻字很不错的
Good for carving. Look at that.
[我们不会迷失方向]
[Music] We won't lose track [music]
[因为有些人的迷途知返]
[Music] 'Cause a part of our backs [music]
[感受那薄翼的重量]
[Music]Feel the weight of wings [music]
[无法难解释他们的坠落]
[Music] Why they fall it's hard to tell [music]
[有一些事情]
[Music]But some things you can't [music]
[你无法买卖]
[Music]Buy or sell [music]
[我们只会伤害我们的所爱]
[Music] Yeah,we only hurt the ones we love [music]
[当我们不需要原因]
[Music] While we don't need a reason [music]
[便放弃了我们珍惜的事物]
[Music] Only give up the thing we deserve [music]
[有些事情]
[Music]And that's something [music]
[需要我们去信仰]
[Music] To believe in [music]
Samantha 有人来看你了
-Samantha? There's a young man here to see you.
嗨
Hey.
你是不是过几天就回去了  是的
- So you're comin' home in a couple of days? - Yeah.
那挺好的   对吧
It's good,right?
是挺好的
It's great.
Jas?
那天晚上……
About that night?
噢
Oh.
我们没必要提了
We don't have to talk about it.
我只想说很抱歉
Just wanted to say that I'm sorry.
呃……我也很抱歉
Well... I'm sorry.
你抱歉什么
What do you have to be sorry for?
我不是个很好的朋友
I haven't been a very good friend.
你一直是我最好的朋友
You've been my best friend.
你永远是我最好的朋友
You'll always be my best friend.
永远
Always.
我真的很爱你
I really do love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
就在这里 知道了吗
That's in there. Got it?
放在 把它放这里
Bring it... Bring it right there.
她怎么样了
How's she doin'?
你想知道的话 你自己干嘛不去看她
If you care so much,why don't you go down and see her?
这关你什么事
What's it to you?
因为我在乎她
Because I do care about her.
不管怎么说 她需要你
For whatever reason,she needs you.
那我应该留下来么
Am I supposed to stay?
我又不是Putnam的 记得吗
I'm not from Putnam,remember?
我还要回到自己的生活
I've got a life to get back to.
你知道吗
Do you know
每次看到她看着你时我有多心痛吗
how much it kills me every time that I see her look at you?
还有每次她喊你的名字时 天哪
Every time I hear her say your name,for Chrisakes?
不管以前看到你跟她一起时我有多么痛心
But no matter how much it tears me up inside to see you with her,
现在我只希望
the one thing that I want right now...
就是你去克服你家那些破事
is for you to get over your shit...
这样你就可以跟陪着她
so that you can be with her.
因为她现在需要你
Because she needs you right now!
不管你承不承认 你也需要她
Whether you want to admit it or not,you need her too.
你不知道我需要什么
You do not know what I need.
你又不了解我
You don't know anything about me.
哦 我现在了解得够多了 不是吗
Well,I know a lot more now,don't I?
我帮你拿
I'll get that for you.
走吧
Let's go.
嘿
Hey.
-我一直在思考 -嗯哈
- I've been thinking. - Uh-huh.
我希望我们的餐馆能按计划开张
I want us to open the restaurant like we planned.
没问题
Okay.
天你知道吗 真希望你没遇见Kelly
Boy,you know,I wish you never met that Kelley.
一些人活了一辈子
Some people live their whole lives...
都没有遇见真爱
and never fall in love.
至少在我的有生之年里
I lived my life,
我恋爱了
and I fell in love.
做你父亲真好
It's good to be your father.
做你的女儿真好
It's good to be your daughter.
嗯
- Earl? - Yeah.
他怎么可以就这么放手了
How could he let our baby go?
[我流过的这些泪水]
[Woman] [Music] These tears I've cried [music]
[我曾经的哭泣]
[Music]I've cried [music]
[汇成无数的汪洋]
[Music]A thousand oceans [music]
[就如同]
[Music]And if it seems [music]
[我在漂浮着]
[Music]I'm flo-oh-oh [music]
[漂浮着]
[Music] Oh-oh-ting [music]
[从天空中坠落在浪尖]
[Music]In air and down this swell [music]
[我无法相信]
[Music]I can't believe [music]
[自己能够]
[Music] That I would keep [music]
[阻止你的飞离]
[Music]Keep you from flying [music]
[我会流着泪水]
[Music]And I would cry [music]
[在那无数的月份里]
[Music]A thousand months [music]
[如果这就是]
[Music]lf that's what it takes [music]
[把你载着回家的代价]
[Music] To sail you home [music]
[载着你回家]
[Music]Sail you home [music]
你经常在这里逗留吗
You hangin' in there?
逗留会就已经足够了
Hanging would definitely describe it.
[我知道那些规则]
[Music]I'm aware what the rules are [music]
[但你知道 我仍然要奔跑]
[Music]But you know that I will run [music]
[我会一直奔跑]
[你知道我将会]
[Music] You know that I'll [music]
[一直在那里等待 因为我爱着你]
[Music]Be here for I love you [music]
[如果我找到你]
[Music]And if I find you [music]
[你还会记得吗]
[Music] Will you still remember [music]
[在梦中玩耍]
[Music]Playing at dreams [music]
轮到是我最害怕的部分了 我们都一样
- This is the part I've been dreading. - You and me both.
各位
Hi,everybody! [Clears Throat]
正如你们所见 我们设了一块崭新的情侣墙
As you all know,we have a brand-new Lover's Wall...
正准备剪彩开放了
just waiting for an inauguration.
送给各位情侣 不管是年轻人还是老年人
For all you lovers,old and young,
欢迎大家刻字 让你们的爱变成永恒
we invite you to come inside and make it permanent.
快进来吧
Come on in!
我想我得鼓鼓勇气
I think I'm going to go brave it.
Samantha 听着 我非常地
Samantha,listen. I am so s...
我想爬上那些桦树枝
I'd like to go by climbing a birch tree...
从那黑色的枝条爬到通向天堂的白色树干
and climb black branches up a snow-white trunk toward heaven,
直到那些树枝无法承受我的重量
till the tree could bear no more,
树枝的一端歪斜把我重重摔落
but dipped its top and set me down again.
对于回去是个不错的结果
That would be good both going and coming back.
还有什么比
One could do worse...
荡着树枝更糟糕的事呢
than be a swinger of birches.
[哦]
[Woman] [Music] Ohh,oh [music]
[嗯]
[Music]Mm-hmm [music]
[嗯嗯]
[有的时候]
[Music] There are times [music]
[我知道你在那里]
[Music]I swear I know you're here [music]
[当我忘却恐惧]
[Music] When I forget about my fears [music]
[感受着你的存在 我亲爱的]
[Music]Feelin'you,my dear [music]
[在看着我]
[Music] Watchin'over me [music]
[我希望知道]
[Music]My hope seeks [music]
[未来会带给我什么]
[Music]For what the future will bring [music]
[当你把握怀抱在你的双翼中]
[Music] When you wrap me in your wings [music]
[带着我]
[Music]And take me [music]
[去你的地方]
[Music] Where you are [music]
[与我一起生活]
[Music] Where you and I will breathe together [music]
[再次相聚]
[Music] Once again [music]
[我们将会在月色朦胧中共舞]
[Music] We'll be dancin' in the moonlight just like [music]
[就像是过去一样]
[Music] We used to do [music]
[你将会对我微笑]
[Music]And you'll be smilin'back at me [music]
[只有在那个瞬间 我才会感受到自由]
[Music] Only then will I be free [music]
[当我处在]
[Music] When I can be [music]
[有你的地方]
[Music] Where you are [music]
[我仍可以凝望着你的脸]
[Man] [Music]And I can see your face [music]
[回味着你的吻]
[Music] Your kiss I still can taste [music]
[思念没有一刻终止]
[Music]Not a memory erased [music]
[我看见属于你的那颗星星]
[Woman] [Music] Oh,I see your star [music]
[将璀璨的光芒投向我]
[Music]Shinin'down on me [music]
[我愿意为你 付出一切]
[Music]And I'd do anything [music]
[如果我可以]
[Duet] [Music]lf I could just [music]
[就在那 在你身旁]
[Music]Be right there [music]
[你在哪]
[Music] Where you are [music]
[你和我会在哪里重逢]
[Music] Where you and I will breathe together [music]
[再次重逢]
[Music] Once again [music]
[我们会像以往那样在月光中共舞]
[Duet] [Music] We'll be dancin' in the moonlight just like [music]
[就像过去一样]
[Music] We used to do [music]
[你仍会朝我幸福地微笑]
[Woman] [Music]And you'll be smilin'back at me [music]
[只有在那个瞬间 我才会感受到自由]
[Music] Only then will I be free [music]
[感受到自由]
[Music] Then I will be free [music]
[带我到你的地方]
[Music]So take me where you are [music]
[噢 亲爱的 有时候当我自私地想]
[Man] [Music]Baby,there are times when selfishly [music]
[我希望你能在我身边]
[Music]I'm wishin'that you were here with me [music]
[所以我拭去你眼中的泪珠]
[Music]So I could wipe the tears from your eyes [music]
[让你看见]
[Music]And make you see [music]
[每个夜里当你进入梦乡时]
[Music] That every night while you are dreamin'[music]
[我在你身边 永远爱你]
[Music]I'm here to guard you from afar [music]
[每当我感受到孤独时]
[Duet] And anytime I feel alone [music]
[我总是合上双眼 梦见有你的地方]
[Music]I close my eyes and dream of where you [music]
[在有你的地方]
[Music]Are [music]
[我们还会在一起 亲爱的]
[Man] [Music]And we will breathe together,baby [music]
[哦]
[Woman] [Music] Ohh [music]
[我们将会在月光下翩然起舞]
[Music] We'll be dancin' in the moonlight [music]
[你仍会朝我幸福地微笑]
[Music]And you'll be smilin'back at me [music]
[只有在那个瞬间 我才会感受到自由]
[Man] [Music] Only then will I be free [music]
[感受到自由]
[Music]And then I will be free [music]
[宝贝 我仍然相信]
[Duet] [Music]Baby,I'll still believe [music]
[哦 我不得不相信]
[Man] [Music] Oh,we got to believe [music]
[我坚信 远方美丽的一天 触碰到你]
[Woman] [Music]I will touch you that sweet day [music]
[带我到有你的地方]
[Music] That you take me there [music]
[有你的地方]
[Man] [Music] Oh,where you are Oh,where you are,yeah [music]
[我仍然相信 我不得不相信]
[Woman] [Music]I've got to believe [music]
[仍然相信 我会一直等着你]
[Man] [Music]I'll always be waiting [music]
[在这里等你  等待那个遥远美丽的一天]
- [Music]Here,yeah  That sweet day,yeah [music]
[只想去有你的地方]
[Man] [Music] Only want to be where you are [music]